Guide to the Gary Stevenson Papers WAG.182
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory
  - [Photographs, Booklet, and Negatives], circa 1992 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - [Photographs, IBT Wallet and IBT Checkbook Cover], undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - [Photographs, Negatives, and Notes], 1995 - 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Roadway Package System, Inc. Background Information", May 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) and Black Lake Family Education Seminar, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME)-Community Service Agency Employees Union (CSAEU) District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Child Care Employees Project Handouts, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Correspondence, 1984 - 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: LM-2s, LM-3s, 1984 - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Labor Support Materials and Employer Support, 1984 - 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Legislative Activity and Testimony, 1987, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Minutes of District Council 1707 Meetings and Union Business, 1987 - 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: NLRB Correspondence, Grant Applications, and Employees' Retirement Fund, 1977 - 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: New York State and New York City Department of Social Services List of Facilities, 1989, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Organizing Materials and Authorizations, 1988 - 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Press and Media, 1987 - 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: "Rank and File" Press, Flyers, and Publicity, 1985 - 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707 (New York)-- Long Island Health Care Services: Research and Lists, 1987 - 1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Fruehauf Trailer Corporation, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - In-House Correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - IBT Memos, Financial Statements, Grievances, and Publications, circa 1982 - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Laminated Pictures (Computer Print-Outs), undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers and Record Book, 1990, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - "Teamsters' Overnite Organizing Campaign Overview" Binder, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707-- NYC Head Start, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707-- Women, Handicapped, and Other Disenfranchised: Correspondence, Activist Groups and Their Literature and Press, Dental Plan (Local 810), Press, and Flyers, 1979 - 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME-CSAEU District Council 1707-- Women, Handicapped, and Other Disenfranchised: Statements and Government Business, 1979 - 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Local 810 [1 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Local 810 [2 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Local 810 [3 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Local 810 [4 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Local 810 [5 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Local 810 [6 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Local 810 [7 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)-- Other Government-Related Materials [1 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)-- Other Government-Related Materials [2 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB)-- Other Government-Related Materials [3 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Notebook, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Various Locals [1 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Various Locals [2 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Various Locals [3 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Contracts and Agreements with Various Locals [4 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Frito-Lay Agreement with Bakery Drivers Local 485 (1992), Minutes of IBT Meeting 3/6/73, and Notes, 1973 - 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - National Master Freight Agreement (NMFA) Organizing, Strike, and Agreement, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Overnite Transportation, Inc.-- Benefits Plan, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Overnite-- Campaign Literature, Organizing Literature, and Blank Forms, 1990 - 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Overnite-- Computer Readout Lists (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Overnite-- Correspondence, 1989 - 1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Overnite-- Flyers, Leaflets, and Teamster Promotional Material, 1990 - 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Overnite-- Home Visit Reports, 1990 - 1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Overnite-- IBT Publications, 1990 - 1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Overnite-- IBT Volunteer Organizing Sign-ups, Authorizations for Representation, and Applications for Membership, 1990 - 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Overnite-- Legals: Petition for Re-Certification at Overnite and Decision and Review Regarding Purolator, 1990 - 1992 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Overnite-- Lists (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Overnite-- Notes of Gary Stevenson, Press, and Photos (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Overnite-- Research, 1990 - 1994. undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Overnite on Behalf of Overnite-- Letters to Employees, Employee Surveys, Employee Scuttlebutt Sheet, and Home Visit Reports, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Company Grievance Procedures and Guidelines, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Correspondence, 1973 - 1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- District Sales Manager/Leader Manual and "General Principles of Sales Management", undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- The Grievance Case of Kimberly Knudson, 1992 - 1994 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Legal Proceedings and NLRB, 1973 - 1994, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Lists, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Organizing Materials and Surveys, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- PepsiCo Annual Report, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Press, Leaflets (Company and Union), and Product Promotion Rage, 1992 - 1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Proxy Statement for Securities Exchange Act, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Research Materials, 1993 - 1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Route Engineering, 1993 - 1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Route Sales Training Program, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Sales Initiatives and Campaigns, 1992 - 1994, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - PepsiCo Frito-Lay-- Securities and Exchange Commission Report, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "Independent Review Board Investigative Report" Volumes I-III Regarding Ronald Carey, U.S. v IBT 88 Civ. 4486 (DNE) and Appeal, and Proposed Rerun Election Plan (Box 12)
  - IBT Publications (and Miscellaneous Union Publications) and Administrative Papers, Correspondence, and Record Books (Box 13)
  - Eaton Corporation-- Agreements with International Union of United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1982 - 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Literature Handed Out (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Local 810-- Able Wire and Fire: Local 810 Correspondence, Organizing Materials, Unions Lists, Research, NLRB Proceedings, Depositions, and Flyer, 1981 - 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Local 810-- Alum-A-Pole: Local 810 Correspondence, NLRB Business, Affidavits, and Research, 1984 - 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Local 810-- Art Suppliers: Correspondence, Financial Transactions, Publicity, Flyers, Lists, and Company Promotional Material, 1982 - 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 810-- Art Suppliers: IBT Flyers, IBT Lists, Authorizations, Organizing Target List, Notes of Gary Stevenson, and Research, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 810-- Art Suppliers: Negotiations/Agreements and Company Manual, 1983 - 1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Local 810-- Baby Watson Cheesecake: Local 810 Correspondence, Organizing Materials, Authorizations, IBT Press, Flyers, Publicity, and Company Correspondence, 1991 - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Local 810-- Baby Watson Cheesecake: NLRB Proceedings, Affidavits and Transcripts, and Approval of Proposed Agreement, 1991 - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Local 810-- Berco Industries: Local 810 Correspondence, Research, and Negotiations/Agreement, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Local 810-- Charrette Art Supplies: Correspondence, Research/Lists, Flyers/Publicity, Company Support, NLRB, Press, and Notes, 1982 - 1984 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Assorted IBT (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Local 810-- Dionics, Inc.: Local 810 Correspondence, Company Correspondence, Research, Organizing Strategies and Authorizations, Flyers and Publicity, NLRB Transactions, and Personal, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Local 810-- Eaton Corporation: Research, Organizing List, Authorizations, 1984 - 1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Local 810-- Freeport Screen: Correspondence, Organizing, Research, Employee Lists, Authorizations, NLRB, Dental, Negotiations/Agreements, Notes and Other, 1985 - 1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Local 810 (and 1199)-- Health and Hospital Employees: Pathmark Correspondence, Research, 1199 Constitution and Bylaws, 1983 - 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Local 810-- Jerry's Artarama: Local 810 Correspondence, Authorizations, Union Lists, Affidavits, Flyers, Company Correspondence, Research, NLRB, Negotiations/Agreement, and Stipulation, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Local 810-- Kerman Protection: Authorizations, List (Company Source), Affidavit of Gary Stevenson, and Agreement, 1983 - 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Local 810-- Knogo Corporation: Local 810 Correspondence, Company Correspondence, Authorizations, Research, Press, Flyers, NLRB Proceedings, and Company Proposals, 1980 - 1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Local 810-- Long Island Nursing Homes: Correspondence, Research, Authorizations, Company Support Materials, Agreements, and Notes (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Local 810-- Melto Metal Products Company, Inc.: Shopman's Local 455 I.A.B.S.O.W. National Labor Relations Board Transactions, October 28, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Local 810-- New York Eye and Ear Hospital: Correspondence, Research, NLRB, Union Flyers, Press, and Company Flyer, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Local 810-- Savin Corporation: Research and Authorizations, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Local 810-- Scientific Metals Inc.: Correspondence, Research, Negotiations/Agreements, Authorizations, Strike, NLRB, Occupational Safety and Health Administration, Notes, and Press, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Local 810-- Sultana Crackers, Inc.: Correspondence, Research, Authorizations, and NLRB, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Local 810-- United Photocopy: Local 810 Correspondence and Tales of Difficulties with Company, Research, Organizing Lists, Authorizations, NLRB, Negotiations/Agreements, and Flyers, 1981 - 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Statements (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Notes on Economics (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Solidarity Day, September 19, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - TDU-IBT (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - "Overnite Transportation Company" by IBT Library and Information Services, IBT Report on Waste Management, Inc., and Various Company Publications (Box 14)
  - State of New York Department of Labor Publications, IBT Reports, United Wire, Metal, and Machine Pension Plan, and Other Materials (Box 15)
  - Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)-- J.P. Stevens: IBT Research and Magazine Piece, 1974 - 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees Local 1000-- Public Service Employee Union Local 424: Correspondence and 424 Briefing Manual, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Local 97 (New Jersey)-- Garden State Parkway: Address by Governor Jim Florio (8/24/1992), Legislation, and Notes of Gary Stevenson (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Local 97 (New Jersey)-- Garden State Parkway: Authorization Cards, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local 97 (New Jersey)-- Garden State Parkway: Company Support/Correspondence and Lists, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Local 97 (New Jersey)-- Garden State Parkway: Organizing- Correspondence, Activities, Flyers, and Press, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Local 111 (New York)-- MCI, Inc.: Correspondence, Booklet for Local 111 Shop Stewards' Conference (12/1/1984), Labor Support Materials, and Company Support Materials (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Local 111 (New York)-- MCI, Inc.: Press, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Local 111 (New York)-- MCI, Inc.: Teamster Press and Flyers, Communications Workers of America (CWA), Postal Telegraph and Telephone International (PTTI), and UE Press, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Local 214 (and 328) IBT (Michigan)-- Agreements and Letter, 1984 - 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Local 247 (and 337) IBT (Michigan)-- Agreements with Bristlecone Nursery and Frank's Nursery, 1982 - 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Local 252 (and 760) IBT (Washington)-- Agreements with Ocean Spray and Milne Fruit Products, 1985 - 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Local 272 (New York)-- Queens Livery Drivers, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Local 327 (Tennessee)-- Ryder: Correspondence, Authorizations, Flyer, Company Information Program, and List of Drivers, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local 519 (Tennessee)-- Fruehauf: Correspondence, Teamsters Publications, Flyers, Home Visit Forms, Lists, and Press, 1995 - 1996 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Local 550 (New York)-- Freihofer Baking Company: Research, Notes, Organizing Communication and Lists, and Authorizations, 1981 - 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Local 638 (Minnesota)-- Agreements with Bachman's, Inc. and Reiss Greenhouse, 1982 - 1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Local 687 (New York)-- Franklin County: Agreements, Petition for a Declaratory Ruling, Proposals, Flyers, and Correspondence, 1991 - 1995 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Local 701 (New Jersey)-- New England Motor Freight (N.E.M.F.) and Local 477 (New Jersey): Correspondence, Research, 1991 N.E.M.F. and International Association of Machinists Agreement, and Press, 1991 - 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Local 707 (New York)-- Correspondence, Litigation, Sign-Up Sheets, In-Company Lists, Teamster Press, and "Rank and File" Press and Flyers, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Local 748 (and 890) IBT (California)-- United Foods: Flyers and Agreement with Yoder Brothers, Inc., 1984, 1987, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Local 803 (New York)-- Brunswick (Long Island) Hospital Nurses' Strike, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Local 804 (New York)-- GSN Trucking Corporation: Certificates of Representation, Lists, and Notes of Gary Stevenson, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Local 804 (New York)-- GSN Trucking Corporation: Company Support, NLRB, and Other Legal, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Local 804 (New York)-- GSN Trucking Corporation: IBT Organizing, Correspondence and Materials, Research, IBT Flyers, and Notes of Gary Stevenson, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Local 804 (New York) and Local 348-S United Food and Commercial Workers Union (New York)-- Quality King Distributors: Agreements and Authorizations, 1993 - 1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Local 814 (New York)-- 7 Santini Brothers Complaint Against "B.A.", 1980 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Local 868 (and 144) IBT (New York)-- ACME Baumann Bus Company, 1992 - 1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Local 1714 IBT (Washington, D.C.) and Local 1 Fraternal Order of Police (Washington, D.C.)-- Organizing Campaign, Corrections Department Correspondence, Affidavit of Gary Hankins (Fraternal Order of Police), and Press from Both Sides, 1992 - 1993 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - [IBT Correspondence and Organizing Materials] (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - [IBT Organizing] (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Local 810-- Organizing (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Local 1115 IBT (New York)-- Joint Board Constitution, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Local 1115 IBT (New York)-- Long Island Nursing Homes: Correspondence, Press, Labor Press, and Long Island Progressive Coalition Materials, 1987 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Local 1115 IBT (New York)-- Long Island Nursing Homes: Litigation and Agreements, 1981 - 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Local 163 International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (New York)-- Cotrell and Leonard; Local 34 Federation of Union Employees-- Yale University; America Postal Workers Union/Occupational Safety and Health Administration-- U.S. Postal Service; Local 111 IBT Coummunications Trade Divison (New York)-- MCI; and Harvard Union of Clerical Workers, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Master List (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Notes and Teaching Aids of Gary Stevenson (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Organizing Leads (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Service Employees International Union Local 144 (New York)-- Hauppauge School District, 1983 - 1986 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU)-Professional Drivers Council (PROD) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Texts on Unionism, Liberties, Civics, etc. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Assorted Materials, Including "Survey [of] Car and Truck Rental Agreements" by IBT Information Center, LM-2s, Correspondence, Flyers, Lobbying and Teaching Materials, Lists, and Articles (Box 16)
  - Andre Jones (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Cet Parks (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Evaluations (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Gary Stevenson-- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Gary Stevenson-- Vouchers, Records, etc. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hannah Roditi (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Local 810-- Berger Industries: Correspondence, Research, Authorizations, List, Flyers, NLRB Correspondence and Arbitration, International Association of Machinists and United Craft and Industrial Workers Unions, Contracts and Bylaws, and LM-1As and LM-2s, 1963 - 1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Local 810 Miscellaneous, 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Local 810 Miscellaneous, 2 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Local 810 Miscellaneous, 3 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Local 810-- Sign-Up Cards (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Mike Curcio (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Ron Joseph (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Sean Murray (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Steve Matthews (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Tony Valenti (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Union Organizing Campaigns (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Vicky Saporta (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - William H. Webster (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Local 810-- Brentano's: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Local 810-- Brentano's: Legals (Affidavits and National Labor Relations Board), 1978 - 1982 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Local 810-- Brentano's: Negotiations and Agreements, 1973 - 1982 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Local 810-- Brentano's: Notes of Gary Stevenson, Lists, Organization and Research, and Sign-Up Cards, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Local 810-- Brentano's: Press and "Rank and File" Flyers, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Local 810-- Candler Coffee Corporation: Correspondence, Research, NLRB, Strike, Negotiations and Agreements, Flyers, and Notes, 1980 - 1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Local 810-- Deer Park Union Free School District: Correspondence, Public Employment Relations Board Grievances and Litigation, Flyers, Lists and Authorizations, Press, Statement from Resident of Deer Park, Company Support, Negotiations and Agreements, Notes, and Research, 1985 - 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Local 810-- Detecto Scales: Transfer of Account and Company Notice, 1976 - 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Local 810-- Fein Container Corporation: Press, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Local 810-- Fisher Scientific: Correspondence, Research and Lists, and Support from Physicians and Scientists for Justice for Fisher Employees, 1991 - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Local 810-- Fisher Scientific: Flyers and Publicity, Press, Authorizations, Strike, Negotiations and Agreements, and Notes, 1991 - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Local 810-- Fisher Scientific: Prospectus, March 18, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Local 810-- Gateway Tire Corporation: Correspondence, Research, Authorizations, and 1981 Agreement, 1981 - 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Local 810-- Long Island Paint Company d/b/a Glen Cove Paint Company: Authorizations, Flyers and Publicity, Research and Lists, NLRB, and Company Support, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Local 810-- Medallion Oil Company, Inc.: Authorizations, Research and Lists, Grievance of Ramon Velez, NLRB, and Rad Oil Company, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Local 810-- National Medical Management: Correspondence, Authorizations, NLRB, Flyers, and Notes, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Local 810-- Victory Memorial Hospital: Local 810, Victory Memorial Hospital Correspondence, Organizing Materials, and Authorizations, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Local 810-- Victory Memorial Hospital: Research and Lists, Flyers and Publicity, and NLRB, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - United Welfare Fund and Prudential Benefits Plan, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Assorted Materials, Including "Airline and Railroad Labor and Employment Law (Volume I)," "Organizing the Construction Industry" Conference Materials, and Training Guides (Box 18)
  - "1992 Supplement to Organizer's Handbook" Edited by Robert J. Pleasure (George Meany Center for Labor Studies) and AFL-CIO Administrative Papers (Box 19)
  - AFL-CIO Manual (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - IBT Freight Organizing Guide (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - IBT Organizing 1993 Semester (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - [IBT Organizing Materials and Research] (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - New Teamsters (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Organizing for Local Unions, circa 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - TDU Organizer's Manual (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Training Materials on Organizing and Teamsters Civil Rights Conference (September 15-17, 1995) (Box 19)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU) Organizing Training Materials (Box 20)
  - Schiff, Chuna, 1959 - 1961 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Schiff, Chuna, 1962 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Seattle, Washington, 1958 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Shenhod, Shlomo, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sherman-Widman, Leah, 1958 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Socialist International, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - South Africa, 1957 - 1958 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - South Bend, Indiana, 1957 - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry, 1959 - 1967 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Union, 1957 - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Union: Aid, 1959 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Union: Aid (Deascan), 1957 - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "Sovietisz Hajmland", 1961 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Springfield, Illinois, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - St. Joseph, Missouri, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - St. Louis, Missouri, 1958 - 1965 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - St. Paul, Minnesota, 1958 - 1962 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Sudarsky, Alta, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, 1956 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Syracuse, New York, 1958 - 1963 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sztern, Leon, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Szwarc, Lejbusz, 1960 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Tacoma, Washington, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Toledo, Ohio, 1958 - 1962 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Toronto, 1957 - 1965 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Traupiansky, Jozef, 1958 - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Tucson, Arizona, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Unions, 1960 - 1963 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - United Hungarian Jews, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - United Restitution Organization, 1953 - 1959 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - United Restitution Organization, 1960 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 31)